https://www.mexil.gr/terms-of-use/

Terms of use - MEXIL LTD - Contract and Home Furniture
Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco ommodo consequat.Monday to Friday: 9-20
Saturday to Sunday: closedarredo@select.com
+1 333 555
HomeFurnitureSofasDesign ChicLoungeCocktail DiningHigh Pop DiningRetroHotelBenchesChairsDiningHigh DiningVienna TrattoriaSoft DiningWooden StyleIndustrial Line ModernLounge ComfortRetro ComfortPolypropyleneCubic LoungeCongressStools + Bar StoolsWooden StoolsContemporary StoolsOttomans PoofTablesCentral Metal BaseCentral Wooden BaseCoffee Side TablesDiningHigh Stand TablesOutdoorDiningDining AluDining BohoBistro AluLounge Alu BohoOutdoor FabricOutdoor poufOutdoor StoolsSofasOutdoor Contemporary sofasOutdoor Wooden sofasOutdoor Synthetic sofasPolypropyleneOutdoor SunbedsOutdoor TablesOutdoor Bar tablesOutdoor Coffee tablesOutdoor UmbrellasWooden ArmchairWooden LoungeAccessoriesOutdoor FamilyOffice SpaceOffice SofasDesksChairsAccessoriesBedroom FurnitureStorage – ShelvingChic HomeChic IdeasEco SofasCatalogsAbout usPortfolioNewsContact us
0
No products in the cart.
HomeFurnitureSofasDesign ChicLoungeCocktail DiningHigh Pop DiningRetroHotelBenchesChairsDiningHigh DiningVienna TrattoriaSoft DiningWooden StyleIndustrial Line ModernLounge ComfortRetro ComfortPolypropyleneCubic LoungeCongressStools + Bar StoolsWooden StoolsContemporary StoolsOttomans PoofTablesCentral Metal BaseCentral Wooden BaseCoffee Side TablesDiningHigh Stand TablesOutdoorDiningDining AluDining BohoBistro AluLounge Alu BohoOutdoor FabricOutdoor poufOutdoor StoolsSofasOutdoor Contemporary sofasOutdoor Wooden sofasOutdoor Synthetic sofasPolypropyleneOutdoor SunbedsOutdoor TablesOutdoor Bar tablesOutdoor Coffee tablesOutdoor UmbrellasWooden ArmchairWooden LoungeAccessoriesOutdoor FamilyOffice SpaceOffice SofasDesksChairsAccessoriesBedroom FurnitureStorage – ShelvingChic HomeChic IdeasEco SofasCatalogsAbout usPortfolioNewsContact us
HomeFurnitureSofasDesign ChicLoungeCocktail DiningHigh Pop DiningRetroHotelBenchesChairsDiningHigh DiningVienna TrattoriaSoft DiningWooden StyleIndustrial Line ModernLounge ComfortRetro ComfortPolypropyleneCubic LoungeCongressStools + Bar StoolsWooden StoolsContemporary StoolsOttomans PoofTablesCentral Metal BaseCentral Wooden BaseCoffee Side TablesDiningHigh Stand TablesOutdoorDiningDining AluDining BohoBistro AluLounge Alu BohoOutdoor FabricOutdoor poufOutdoor StoolsSofasOutdoor Contemporary sofasOutdoor Wooden sofasOutdoor Synthetic sofasPolypropyleneOutdoor SunbedsOutdoor TablesOutdoor Bar tablesOutdoor Coffee tablesOutdoor UmbrellasWooden ArmchairWooden LoungeAccessoriesOutdoor FamilyOffice SpaceOffice SofasDesksChairsAccessoriesBedroom FurnitureStorage – ShelvingChic HomeChic IdeasEco SofasCatalogsAbout usPortfolioNewsContact us
Home  /  Terms of useREAD CAREFULLY THE TERMS OF USE OF THIS WEBSITEWelcome to the site of mexil.gr. On the occasion of your visit to our website mexil.gr we inform you about the terms of use. Mexil through its official website www.mexil.gr presents the company’s profile all products sorted by category and material, catalogs, the portfolio with the projects we have carried out, the company’s news. Our company, taking all the necessary security measures, has on its website an SSL certificate for your secure browsing.I agree and I accept:The Privacy Policy applies to all users of the website. This Privacy Policy applies to the collection and use of your personal information by the company.We collect the data you give us, when completing the contact form available on our website for your best service.The personal data you fill in the contact form is your name, phone number, email address. According to the terms of use, Mexil is entitled to keep your personal data for statistical purposes, as defined in Law 2472/97 about GDPR.Personal data through the website is not disclosed, transferred or transferred to third parties.To receive all our new newsletters, discounts, offers immediately by email, select «I want to receive newsletters and information about products, news and events.» You can at any time choose to stop sending newsletters by contacting us at info@mexil.grCookies Policy:Our company, based on the new technologies and the new tools of Google, uses cookies to make your navigation on our website even better and easier. These are tools that help us understand how visitors use our website. “Cookies” are small text files that are stored on the device you use to connect to the Internet without receiving a file / document on your device.Ad Cookies:  With ad cookies you can see ads related to your interests, so that we do not bother you with unwanted messages.Analytics cookies: They give us the ability to evaluate the effectiveness of our site’s various features so that we can continually improve your experience (Facebook pixel, Google Analytics)Preferences Cookies: These cookies “memorize” your preferences while browsing our site so that we can suggest the right products according to you needs.If you have any comments or questions, please do not hesitate to send us an e-mail to: info@mexil.gr or you may use the contact form.About usMexil is a professional contract furniture company. Nowadays the company relies in modern design and advanced manufacturing technology, to meet the demanding challenges of the European & Global market.
InformationsHomeFurnitureCatalogsAbout usPortfolioNewsTerms of useContact usThessaloniki 2 Poseidonos Str., Pylaia, 55535
Junction shopping center “Macedonia”
+30 2310 383 000-1 Monastiriou 101, 54627 FACTORY
6th km Thessaloniki-LagadaAthens 44 Kifisias avenue, Marousi, 15125
+30 210 6180600Heraklion Crete 289 62 Martiron avenue, 71303
+30 2810 323901
info@mexil.grCopyright © 2020 - Developed by MMS AdvertisingIndoor and Outdoor, Contract and Home Furniture
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. AcceptPrivacy policy
